// A file for all my questions.

const myQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "For which movie did Steven Spielberg win his first Oscar for Best Director?",
    a: "E.T.",
    b: "Schindler's List",
    c: "Jaws",
    d: "Jurassic Park",
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which film won an Oscar for Best Makeup and Hairstyling despite having a budget of $250",
    a: "Dallas Buyers Club",
    b: "The Blair Witch Project",
    c: "Paranormal Activity",
    d: "Lord of the Rings",
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Who played Private Ryan in Saving Private Ryan",
    a: "Tom Sizemore",
    b: "Edward Burns",
    c: "Tom Hanks",
    d: "Matt Damon",
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "In The Big Lebowski, which band does The Dude hate?",
    a: "The Beetles",
    b: "Eagles",
    c: "The Rolling Stones",
    d: "Steely Dan",
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Helena Bonham Carter and Meat Loaf appear in which film?",
    a: "Fight Club",
    b: "The Rocky Horror Picture Show",
    c: "Rocky",
    d: "Waynes World",
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "On which planet was Superman born?",
    a: "Saturn",
    b: "Mars",
    c: "Kypton",
    d: "Earth",
    correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Who directed th 1997 film Jackie Brown?",
    a: "Tim Burton",
    b: "James Cameron",
    c: "Steven Spielberg",
    d: "Quentin Taratino",
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many times was Leonardo DiCaprio nominated for an Oscar before winning Best Actor in 2016",
    a: "3",
    b: "4",
    c: "5",
    d: "6",
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Which social network is the film The Social Network based on?",
    a: "Instagram",
    b: "MySpace",
    c: "Twitter",
    d: "Facebook",
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Which sport is the subject of the 1993 film Cool Runnings?",
    a: "Bobsleigh",
    b: "Ice Hockey",
    c: "Long Distance Running",
    d: "Ice Skating",
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
];
